https://antiquewireless.org/homepage/privacy-policy/

Home » Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyAntique Wireless Association Privacy StatementThe Antique Wireless Association (“AWA”) is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our Website or use our Website to purchase tickets, make a donation, become an AWA Member, sign up to receive our e-newsletter, or participate in our surveys. The AWA takes reasonable steps to protect your privacy and to ensure that you are notified of what information you are providing to us and how that information will be used.This Privacy Statement applies to the online activities of the AWA. It does not apply to websites that are linked to, but not controlled by, the AWA, such as social media sites (YouTube, Facebook, Twitter, Instagram. etc.), and the sites of our sponsors and affiliates that may be linked through the Website. These third party sites may or may not have privacy policies of their own; please consult those sites for their applicable policies.WHAT WE COLLECT & WHY WE COLLECT ITNon-Personal InformationOur Website automatically gathers and stores Non-Personal Information, which may include:The IP address from which you access our Website;The name of the domain from which you accessed our Website (i.e. the page that linked you to AntiqueWireless.org);The type of browser and operating system you use to access our Website;The date and time you access our Website; and the pages, files, documents, and links you access on our Website.We collect Non-Personal Information to help us evaluate and improve how our Website works and to learn how and from where visitors access it. This information is stored and used in the aggregate, meaning that it is not tied to your name and does not identify you as an individual. This statistical information may be provided to third parties. Neither the AWA nor any third party will use this information to contact you personally unless you personally request us to do so.Personal InformationPersonal Information includes information that identifies you as an individual and is linked to your name. Personal Information may include:Your name;Your email address;Your mailing address;Your telephone number;Credit card or other financial information; andDemographic information (e.g. age, size of household).The AWA will only collect Personal Information that is voluntarily and knowingly provided, such as when you fill out a membership, donation, or order form, or if you sign up for a program or event, agree to participate in a survey, or request communications from the AWA.The AWA will use this information to respond to your specific inquiry, request, or order. Sometimes the AWA may use third party vendors to perform certain services on our behalf, such as mailings, email distribution, order fulfillment, and shipping; these vendors will have access to Personal Information to the extent required to perform their functions, but will not use that information for any other purposes.The AWA may also use Personal Information you submit to the AWA in order to communicate with you about exhibitions, programs, membership, development, surveys, special events, and other the AWA news that may be of interest to you and for other marketing and promotional purposes. You will always have the opportunity to decline further communications (see below for instructions on how to opt out).The AWA will disclose information, if required, for purposes of law enforcement or the enforcement of the AWA’s or a third party’s rights, such as intellectual property rights and laws relating to fraud. In response to a request by a federal, state, or local law enforcement agency or to a court-issued subpoena, the AWA can (and you authorize the AWA to) disclose your Personal Information to the extent that the AWA reasonably believes necessary to comply with the request or subpoena. The AWA may also use your Personal Information when it is reasonably necessary to satisfy an applicable law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable government request; enforce an agreement between you and the AWA, including potential violations thereof; detect, prevent, investigate or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues; or protect against imminent harm to the safety, property, or rights of the AWA, its visitors, or the public as required or permitted by law.Survey ResponsesThe AWA may invite you to participate in one of our surveys, which provide the AWA with valuable feedback about our publications, programs and information or about Antique Wireless Museum visitors’ experiences, preferences, and needs.These surveys may request certain Personal Information from you, including household and demographic data such as age, marital status, size of household, etc. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to disclose this information to us. You may be given the opportunity to opt in to further communications from the AWA during the survey, but your contact information will not be associated with your survey responses or the provided demographic information.The AWA may use third party service providers to conduct surveys or analyze survey data; such service providers will not use your Personal Information for any other purpose. We will not share any Personal Information gathered through a survey with other third parties without giving you prior notice and an opportunity to opt out.Children’s InformationThe AWA does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. If Personal Information regarding a child is required for program participation or similar reasons, the AWA will collect this information from the child’s parent or guardian.HOW TO OPT OUT OF ANTIQUE WIRELESS ASSOCIATION COMMUNICATIONSYou may opt out of receiving further communications from the AWA at any time. Any communication sent to you by the AWA will include an unsubscribe link or other instructions that will allow you to opt out of future communications or you may send a request to opt out to Director@AntiqueWireless.org.INFORMATION SECURITYThe Website uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption to process online transactions. Additionally, the AWA takes other precautions to protect the Personal Information it receives, both online and offline, from unauthorized access, as do the third party service providers who work with us.Links on Antique Wireless Association’s Website:From time to time, AWA may, with permission from the website owner, decide to link to websites that we determine may be of interest to our visitors. These websites may offer educational, mission-related, or other resources and may be owned or controlled by other third parties. We are not responsible for the content of any linked website or social media site, any link(s) contained in any linked website, or any changes or updates to the information contained in such websites. AWA provides links to third party websites only as a convenience and the inclusion of any such link on AWA website does not imply AWA’s endorsement of either the website, the organization operating such website, or any products or services of that organization. A visit to any website or page from AWA’s website through any such link is done entirely at your own risk.If you find any link on AWA’s website or any linked website objectionable for any reason, you may contact us. Requests to remove links will be considered, but AWA will have no obligation to do so or to respond directly to you.ACCEPTANCE OF TERMSBy using the AWA’s Website you signify your acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree with the terms above please do not use our Website.Occasional changes may be made to this Statement as new services and content are added or to reflect changes in the AWA’s policies. Visitors to the Website are encouraged to check this page periodically to stay informed of the AWA current Privacy Statement. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of changes to its terms will indicate acceptance of those changes.QUESTIONS AND COMMENTSIf you have questions or comments about this Privacy Statement, please contact us in one of the following ways:Antique Wireless Association / PO Box 421 / Bloomfield, NY 14469(585) 257-5119 (Staff is available on Tuesdays all day and Saturday afternoons; voice mail is available)Director@antiquewireless.orgThe AWA will use reasonable efforts to respond promptly to requests, questions, and concerns regarding this Policy Statement.Privacy Statement Last Updated March 2020Login Username or email address *
Password *
Login
Remember me
Lost your password?
Search for:
HomeNewsMuseumVisiting and ToursMuseum VisitationMuseum Virtual TourCurators ChoiceFacilitiesKnowledge CollegeAWA MonographsCollection InsightsVolunteersAWA Awards and HonorsAWA Leadership Honors AwardsWeb LinksFor EducatorsCorporate SponsorsEventsEvents CalendarEducational Classes2020 Fall Radio Fab Lab ClassesLearn It, Build It, Fix It ClassesAfter HoursOn-the-AirAmateur RadioBuild InfoWeekly AWA NetsContestsBruce Kelley 1929 QSO PartyLinc Cundall Memorial CW ContestAmplitude Modulation QSO PartyJohn Rollins Memorial DX ContestSpring Meet2019 Spring Meet ReviewAnnual Conference2020 AWA Virtual Conference2020 Virtual Peoples ChoicePrevious Con. ReviewSpy Radio OperatorsRecent AwardsConf. Awards RulesConf. ContactsConf. Preliminary ScheduleMedia-PubsMuseum SparksMuseum Sparks ArchiveAWA JournalJournal On-Line ArchiveJournal StaffAWA ReviewAWA Review Master IndexAWA Review ArchiveAWA Review Vol. 33Centennial of KDKAAWA Review Vol. 32Nikola Tesla ArticleAWA Review Vol 31 ArticleAWA Review Submission TipsAWA Guide to Review AuthorsAWA Journal Review IndexAWA YouTube ChannelWebsiteGatewayMembershipClasses of MembershipAWA Fellows ClassAWA FellowsMembership ApplicationsGift MembershipsAbout UsFAQWebsite LoginDonateVision Mission and Core ValuesOrganizationMuseum HistoryCampus and FacilitiesMedia CenterOur CollectionBoard, Officers and StaffCommitteesContactsWebsite AdministratorPrivacy PolicyStorePurchase PCB ItemsPCB Item 1PCB Item 2Membership – On-LineMembership – Mail-InDonate – On-LineDonate – Mail-InAWA Store Mail-In Ordering
